WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
As for me...
I stand by my words.
That's... my Ninja Way!
If you die, there will be no dreams,
no nothing!
Just get out of the way!
Run away!
Just like our wager,
I will definitely win
that unlucky necklace from you.
I...
I will absolutely not die
until I've become Hokage!
This way, I can hold on to you.
Here I go!
I-It can't be...
The Fifth Hokage
a Life or Death battle!
Rasengan!
This is...?!
Way to go, Naruto.
That Nine-Tailed Fox kid...
a kid like that,
doing a technique like that...
I-It can't be...
He can't be, really...
In only one week,
that Rasengan...
You... Even after you received
that Jutsu...?!
I gathered the Chakra in my stomach,
and before I received the Jutsu
I had started healing.
The reason why Orochimaru-sama favors me...
is not because of my use of Jutsu
or my sense for Jutsu...
It is because my recuperative power.
The power to energize cells
and make new cells.
On the other hand...
I've used up almost all of my Chakra.
That Jutsu...
seems it was Naruto-kun's last effort...
Wh-What?!
I-It can't be...
Even with my powers of recuperation,
this much damage.
I don't... have... enough Chakra.
Arrhythmia!
Damn! His heart muscle is in tatters...
Why did that happen...?
That moment?!
At that moment of release...
did he shred the muscles
around his heart...?
Stop shaking!
Hey, Gamakichi nii-chan.
Are we really getting a snack?
That guy looks like he's going to die.
You're annoying! Be quiet!
It's all over... for Naruto-kun.
I... cut... his heart's Chakra Network
which restores the strength...
through the Nine-Tail's Chakra...
With all my strength.
In order to eliminate the possibility
that he would heal with his own power.
There's no way he can recover...
Even with you.
Shut up!
I'll kill you later...
He's stopped breathing...!
Dammit!
It's dark...
Dark...
Why is it getting dark?
My strength is... Why...?
What...?
Don't die...
Don't die!
The bet...
I won it.
I-It's impossible...
"Hokage is... my dream," eh?
For the last time...
Just one more time...
I want to bet on you...
That child, he's not well...
Tsunade is a medical specialist.
Don't worry, there's no need to
worry about Naruto's body.
That's not what I meant.
What?
Your battle is with me,
there's no time to look away.
Who would have imagined this?
If that child is found by the Akatsuki,
there will be trouble.
In other words,
if I'm to kill him...
now is the time!
Damn!
He's aiming at this child!
Tsunade... You're the only one
I wasn't going to kill...
If that child lives,
there will be trouble in the future
on a variety of levels.
Don't get in my way.
This is one child...
I will absolutely protect!
Trembling at the sight of blood,
why would you, one of the Sannin,
risk your life to protect that Genin kid?
To protect...
my hometown... the Leaf Village...!
To protect the Leaf Village...?
Because... because...
this small child...
is the kid who will become
Hokage some day...
What utter nonsense...
By the way...
to hell with Hokage!
Only a fool does that job.
To hell with Hokage!
The wishes of the two...
More importantly, Tsunade-sama,
your wish...
Have you forgotten your dream?
The successive lines of Hokage
have protected
the Leaf Village and
and those living in it.
They brought troubled times under control
and helped the village to prosper.
They risked their lives
for this dream, this ideal!
Anyone who makes fun of the old man
and the Fourth Hokage...
It doesn't matter if
you are a woman!
I'll beat you with everything I have!
And now,
I also will put my life on the line!
If your life is worth throwing away
for a kid like him...!
Then dying now would be
a fitting end!
All that's left... is Naruto-kun.
Tsunade-sama!
Make it in time!
She's still able to move even
after I pierced her down to her lungs!
You mean you'll still protect that kid?!
That's what I said...
From now...
I'm putting my life on the line!
You, half-dead corpse!
No matter how cool you try to be,
your trembling doesn't stop.
You can't get away from
the curse of hemophobia.
And yet, why would you
take the blows for that kid?
Why would you battle for the Leaf?
No way!
Tsunade's trembling has...
has stopped?
That is because... I am...
the Leaf Village's... Fifth Hokage!
That sign is?!
Tsunade-sama has conquered
her fear of blood,
but that's...
What are you saying you'll do,
after all this time?
You can't fight with that wound
even if you've conquered your fear.
W-Wait! I'll treat that wound.
So don't release that seal!
Tsunade: Release the Secret Seal!
Ninja Art: Mitotic Regeneration!
What is this Jutsu...?!
It looks like I'm not the only one
who develops new Jutsu.
What in the world is this Jutsu?
Well...
For many years I've stored Chakra
in my forehead.
The mass of Chakra stimulated
a variety of proteins.
The number of times my cells divide
speeds to a dizzying rate...
The cells rebuild...
and all the organs and body systems
are revitalized.
It's not the ability to restore,
it's the ability to reincarnate.
That means I won't die... from battles.
But the number of times a person's cells
divide in their lifetime is fixed...
If that is sped up,
it essentially shortens the life!
Tsunade-sama!
That action is...
Orochimaru-sama!
Come out!
Hurry!
Ino, inu, saru, Tori, hitsuji!
— Summoning Jutsu!
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
The time to conclude this long, fateful
confrontation has come, Orochimaru.
You have sunk too deeply into vice.
You are no longer a comrade!
Comrade? How repulsive.
That word makes me shiver.
I will bring you down!
Today is the last day that
we are called Sannin!
Next time:
"The Three-Way Deadlock Battle."